[
	{
		"id": "quiz-1",
		"ur-PK_display": "درست جواب کا انتخاب کریں",
		"en-US_display": "Select the correct answer:",
		"questions": [
			{
				"name": "q1",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "______ الكلبُ يَنبَحُ",
				"options": {
					"a": "مَنذُ",
					"b": "ما زَال", 
					"c": "ما صارَ"
				},
				"answer": ["b"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q2",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "______ القمر أرزقًا",
				"options": {
					"a": "أصبحت",
					"b": "أصبح", 
					"c": "ظل", 
					"d": "ظلَّت"
				},
				"answer": ["a"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q3",
				"input": "checkbox",
				"question": "ليسَ المُعَلِّمُ ______",
				"options": {
					"a": "غَائبًا",
					"b": "بِغَائبٍ", 
					"c": "حَاضِرًا", 
					"d": "بِحَاضِرِ"
				},
				"answer": ["a","b","c","d"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q4",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "النَّاسُ رَغِبَ _______ المُتَسَوِّل",
				"options": {
					"a": "مِن",
					"b": "إلَي", 
					"c": "عَن", 
					"d": "عِندَ"
				},
				"answer": ["c"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q5",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "القِطُّ رَغِبَ _______ اللَبن",
				"options": {
					"a": "مِن",
					"b": "إلَي", 
					"c": "عَن", 
					"d": "عِندَ"
				},
				"answer": ["b"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q6",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "ذَهَبَ الطَّائرُ _______ الحشَرَة",
				"options": {
					"a": "بِ",
					"b": "لِ",
					"d": "كَ"
				},
				"answer": ["a"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "quiz-2",
		"ur-PK_display": "درست جواب کا انتخاب کریں",
		"en-US_display": "Select the correct answer:",
		"questions": [
			{
				"name": "q1",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "Choose correct translations: (Try to read it)",
				"options": {
					"a": "حَاوِل قَرَيت",
					"b": "حَاوِل إِن تَقرَءَهُ", 
					"c": "حَاوِل أَن تَقرَءَهُ",
					"d": "حَاوِل قِرَاءَتِهِ"
				},
				"answer": ["c", "d"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q2",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "without me",
				"options": {
					"a": "مِن دُونِ",
					"b": "مِن دُونِي", 
					"c": "مِن دُونَنِي"
				},
				"answer": ["b"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q3",
				"input": "checkbox",
				"question": "(During)",
				"options": {
					"a": "أثناء",
					"b": "في", 
					"c": "بينا"
				},
				"answer": ["a","c"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q4",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "?What are you (searching for)",
				"options": {
					"a": "بحث عن",
					"b": "بحث", 
					"c": "يجد"
				},
				"answer": ["a"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q5",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "She (laughed at) me",
				"options": {
					"a": "ضحكت",
					"b": "ضحك", 
					"c": "ضحك من", 
					"d": "ضحكت من"
				},
				"answer": ["d"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			},
			{
				"name": "q6",
				"input": "radio",
				"question": "!Get out of here",
				"options": {
					"a": "إذهب هناك!",
					"b": "إذهب عن هنا!",
					"d": "إذهب إلَي هنا!"
				},
				"answer": ["b"],
				"style": "font-size: 18px;font-weight: bold;"
			}
		]
	}
]